Finding Aid to Framed Items from the Collections of The Bancroft Library
The Bancroft Library
- Individual Framed Items
  - Gold diggins [sic] of California, August 23rd, 1849; Unknown; BANC PIC 1989.020--FR; 1 painting on paper: watercolor, pencil, and ink; visible image 30.8 x 39 cm. Handwritten title and date (LC): Gold diggins of California. Drawn August 23rd 1849.
    Gold mining site along river showing numerous miners at work as well as a few Indians, tents, and campsites visible on bank. Some claims are identified by name: Essex Company, A. J. Bryant, W. A. Egery, Sajean Co., B. R. and P. S. W., B. R. store house of Boston Co. on hill.
    Watercolors; Gold mines and mining -- California -- Pictorial works
  - Masonic Home of California, [Decoto, Calif.], [ca. 1890]; Louis Roesch Co.; BANC PIC 1991.025--FR; 1 print: lithograph, color; visible image 52.7 x 76.2 cm. Printed title (LC). Printed (LL): Louis Roesch Co. Lith. S.F.
    Depicts the Masonic Home for the Aged in Decoto, Calif., surrounded by hills.
    Lithographs -- Color; Masonic Homes of California -- Pictorial works; Decoto (Union City, Calif.) -- Buildings, structures, etc. -- ictorial works; Masonic Home for the Aged (Decoto, Calif.) -- Pictorial works
  - [Southwest canyon landscape], [before 1938]; Buff, Conrad; BANC PIC 1991.035--FR; 1 painting on panel: oil; visible image 38.6 x 58.7 cm. Handwritten (verso): Painted by / Conrad Buff / noted artist. Newspaper clippings on verso dated 1938. Includes biographical information on artist (from Los Angeles Times?).
    Rugged mountain landscape.
    Oil paintings; Landscapes (Representations) -- Southwest; Southwest, New -- Pictorial works
  - [The independent gold hunter on his way to California: I neither borrow nor lend], [between 1849 and 1852]; Nathaniel Currier; BANC PIC 1991.077--FR; 1 print: lithograph, handcolored; visible image 34.3 x 22.6 cm. Printed title (LC). Printed (LL): Lith. & pub. by N. Currier; (LR): 152 Nassau St[reet], cor[ner] of Spruce, N[ew] Y[ork]. Date based on lithographer/publisher active dates at above location.
    Prospector loaded down with mining tools, cookware, knives, and food items making his way to California; signpost displaying distances to California and St. Louis.
    Lithographs -- Hand-colored; Caricatures -- Hand-colored; Miners -- California -- Pictorial works
  - Church at Monterey, Calif., 1849 July 17.; Sully, Alfred; BANC PIC 1993.025--FR; 1 painting on paper: watercolor and pencil; visible image 18.2 x 24.5 cm. Handwritten title and date (LR): Church at Monterey, Calif. / Church at Monterey, Calif. / July 1849.
    View of the church at the Monterey Presidio. Priest and resident greeting each other in front of building; figure of woman to left. Low hills in background; two white-washed buildings to the right. Bell support structure in foreground.
    Watercolors; Pencil works; Catholic Church -- California -- Monterey; Church buildings -- California -- Monterey
  - Bird's eye view of Sacramento, Calif., [1877?]; W.W. Elliott Lithographers; R.H.; Sacramento Union/Daily Record Union/Weekly Union; BANC PIC 1993.026--FR; 1 print: lithograph, color; visible image 58.2 x 90.2 cm. Printed (LL): W.W. Elliott Lith. S.F. for Record Union; (LR): Copyrighted.
    Content/DescriptionView of city looking east from river. Marginal images include prominent residences, businesses, and public buildings. Businesses include the Crocker Art Gallery, Weinsock & Lubin, Western Hotel, Pioneer Milling, Booth & Co., Bassett & Minford, Alsip, Waterhouse & Lester, Whittier Fuller & Co., Huntington Hopkins & Co., Voorhies & Co., McCreary & Co. Residences include Crocker, Lewis, Richardson, Steffens and Cummings.
    Bird's-eye views; Chromolithographs; Sacramento (Calif.) -- Pictorial works
  - Near Chinaman's Fishing Camp, Monterey, California, 1892, Stuart, James Everett; BANC PIC 1994.017--FR; 1 painting: oil; visible image 59.7 x 105.7 cm. Painted signature and date (LL): J.E. Stuart. / 1892. Title from label on verso. Acquisition information on label on verso.
    View of lonely coastline with fishermen carrying baskets near water; structure for processing catch on hill to right.
    Oil paintings; Chinese -- California -- Monterey Bay Region -- Pictorial works
  - Birds-eye view of Prescott, A.T. looking north east: sketched by C.J. Dyer., [1885]; Dyer, C.J.; BANC PIC 1994.024--FR; 1 print: lithograph, color; visible image 51 x 77 cm. Printed title (LC). Printed (LR): sketched by C. J. Dyer.
    Large central view, with vignette of Prescott in 1864, two vignettes of mountains in the area, and at bottom several vignettes of public and business buildings. Marginal views include Thumb Butte, Granite Mountain, Sherman House, store of M. Goldwater and son, L. Bashford and Co., Diana saloon (billiards hall), Geo. H Curry jewelry store, office of Dr. F. K. Ainsworth. Also includes public school, county courthouse, Prescott in 1864 as well as references to numerous other businesses, churches, ect. Key to prominent locations.
    Lithographs -- Color; Bird's-eye views; Prescott (Ariz.) -- Pictorial works; Cityscape prints -- Arizona -- Prescott -- 1885
  - House with Picket Fence, [19--?]; H.B.; BANC PIC 1994.037--FR; 1 painting on academy board: acrylic; visible image 12.2 x 17.2 cm. Painted initials (LL): H. B.
  - Bird's eye view of the City of Petaluma, Sonoma County, California: drawn by Augustus Koch., 1871; Koch, Augustus; Britton & Rey; BANC PIC 1995.041--FR; 1 print: lithograph, color and hand color; visible image 58.5 x 71.3 cm. Printed title and date (LC). Printed (LL): drawn by Augustus Koch; (LR): lith. Britton & Ray S.F.
    View overlooking town along river and outlying areas. Streets labeled, points of interest numbered.
    Lithographs -- Color; Bird's-eye views; Petaluma (Calif.) -- Pictorial works; Petaluma (Calif.) -- Aerial views
  - Gilroy: Santa Clara County California, 1885; Blake, F.W.; BANC PIC 1996.017--FR; 1 print: lithograph, color; visible image 43.8 x 58 cm. Printed title and date (LC). Printed (LC): F. W. Blake, Pub., Gilroy, Cal.
    Content/DescriptionBird's eye view of town and surrounding land with marginal images of local businesses, churches, and public buildings, including Railroad House, Gilroy Advocate (F. W. Blake), Southern Pacific Hotel (Geo. Seaman), Gilroy Flouring Mills (Smith Bros.), Merchant Taylor (Dunham), Tryon & Salisbury Undertakers, Gilroy Brewery (Harold & Casey), S.P.R.R. Streets labeled, points of interest numbered.
    Lithographs -- Color; Bird's-eye views; Gilroy (Calif.) -- Pictorial works
  - Santa Rosa, Sonoma County, California., 1885; W.W. Elliott Lithographers; BANC PIC 1996.027--F; 1 print: lithograph; sheet 60.5 x 78 cm. Printed title (LC). Printed explanatory key to locations in central image (LC below title). Printed: (LR below title): Elliott & Co. Lith. Oakland.
    Content/DescriptionLarge central image is overview of city, showing buildings, farms, and Santa Rosa Creek. Marginal images of prominent businesses, public buildings and residences include court house, Eagle Hotel, city hall and library, New York Hotel, Howe's Boots & Shoes, Sonoma Democrat office, Fashion Stable, Pacific Methodist College, E.A. Seegelken's store & saloon, Henry Krunke residence, Athenaeum, Republican office, Young Ladies College, Occidental Hotel, F. Berka lumber yard, Santa Rosa Planning Mills, Mark L. McDonald residence (Mableton). In lower left corner is advertisement for real estate broker Guy E. Grosse with text.
    Bird's-eye views; Lithographs; Santa Rosa (Calif.) -- Pictorial works
  - Chinese, Tolumne [sic] County, Southern Mines, California, [1858]; Kuchel, Charles Conrad; Kuchel & Dresel; Britton & Rey; BANC PIC 1997.004--FR; 1 print: lithograph, handcolored; visible image 33.2 x 45.5 cm. Printed title (LC). Printed (LL): from nature on stone by Kuchel & Dresel, 176 Clay St. S.F.; (LR): Printed by Britton & Rey; (LR in image): CCK [Charles Conrad Kuchel].
    Content/DescriptionView of town surrounded by marginal images of local businesses and mining claims including: Cobb & Taylor, Miller & Co., Vedder & Cutler, Cogswell and Graham, Raymond & Peacock, Garretts Hotel, Eagle Hotel, Eureka claim, Garswiller & Meloney claim, Schermans & Reeler claim, and Campo Salvado, East Chinese.
    Lithographs -- Hand-colored; Bird's-eye views; Chinese Camp (Calif.) -- Pictorial works; Mining districts -- California -- Tuolumne County -- Pictorial works; Mines and mineral resources -- California -- Tuolumne County -- Pictorial works
  - [Portrait of Ann Flint], 1899; Gilbert, R.; BANC PIC 1997.018--FR; 1 drawing: pastel; visible image 54.1 x 44.8 cm. Handwritten signature and date (LR): R. Gilbert- / 1899-.
    Bust portrait.
    Portraits; Pastels (Visual works); Flint, Ann -- Portraits
  - [Portrait of Lawrence Ferlinghetti], c1974; Le Blanc, Peter; BANC PIC 1997.037--FR; 1 print: color; 68.5 x 44.2 cm. Handwritten signature (LL): © Peter Le Blanc 1974. Numbered (LR): [?]/8.
    Full length portrait of the Beat generation poet and City Lights Books store owner seated in chair with an open book in his lap and a large coat or cloak over his shoulders.
    Portraits; Ferlinghetti, Lawrence -- Portraits; Poets, American -- 20th century -- Portraits
  - [Camp Teller], [ca. 1890-1892]; Gremke, Henry Dietrich Richard.; BANC PIC 1998.019--FR; 1 painting on panel: oil; visible image 19.2 x 32.8 cm. Painted signature (LR) H.D. Gremke. Handwritten title and date on verso (UC): Camp Teller: South Pacific Coast Rail[ink?] / 544 38th St. Oakland, Ca. / ... / ca. 1890-92. Biographical and auction information attached to verso of panel.
    Cluster of buildings and a train on the South Pacific Coast Railway stop at Camp Teller, between Glenwood and Felton in the Santa Cruz Mountains, Calif. Possibly a study from a series of murals of stations commissioned by the Southern Pacific and Santa Fe Railroads, most of which have been lost or destroyed.
    Oil paintings; Santa Cruz Mountains (Calif.) -- Pictorial works; Railroads -- California -- Santa Cruz County -- Pictorial works; South Pacific Coast Railroad -- Pictorial works
  - [Miners camp on the Calaveras River, California in 1849], [1849 or later]; [Hedlim? Hellim? Kellim Kedlim? Kiellim?], C.B.; BANC PIC 1998.029--FR; 1 painting: oil; visible image 24.4 x 34.6 cm. Handwritten label (verso): Miners camp on the Calaveras River California in 1849 / by C.B. [Hedlim? Hellim? Kellim? Kedlim? Kiellim?]
    View of miners, tents [made from green leaves?] and a campfire, with the river and mountains in the background.
    Oil paintings; Landscapes (Representations) -- California; Miners -- California -- Pictorial works; Gold mines and mining -- California -- Calaveras River -- Pictorial works; Mining camps -- California -- Pictorial works
  - The Pacific slope, reached via the Union Pacific system., [189?]; Unknown; BANC PIC 1998.040--F; 1 print: lithograph, color; 46 x 96 cm. Printed title (LC). Printed logo (LL and LR on either side of title): Union Pacific, the Overland Route, world's pictorial line.
    Bird's-eye view of southern and central California, as seen from coast, showing relief, cities and towns, and rail lines connecting them.
    Lithographs -- Color; Bird's-eye views; Union Pacific Railroad Company -- Maps; Railroad travel -- California -- Pictorial works; California -- Description and travel -- Pictorial works; California, Southern -- Pictorial works
  - [Portrait of Helen Wills Roark], [192-?]; John, Augustus; BANC PIC 1999.026--FR; 1 painting on linen: oil; visible image 73.9 x 45.2 cm. Painted inscription and signature (LL): To / Helen Wills / in affectionate homage / Augustus John. Engraved plaque (LC of frame): Helen Wills / benefactor / Helen Wills Neurosciences Institute. Stamp (verso of frame): frame / Kopp / Detroit.
    Half length.
    Oil paintings; Wills, Helen, -- 1905- -- Portraits
  - [California Landscape], [ca. 1890]; Yelland, Raymond Dabb; BANC PIC 19xx.009--FR; 1 painting: oil; visible image 60 x 95 cm. Painted signature (LR): R. D. Yelland. Title from label on verso. oil on canvas
    Landscape at dusk with oak trees to the right and a small house in the center.
    Landscapes; Dwellings
  - [San Francisco Bay Felucca], [ca. 1865]; Denny, Gideon Jacques; BANC PIC 19xx.012--FR; 1 painting: oil; visible image 74.5 x 100.3 cm. UC #328 (verso UL). Title on verso backing board and label.
    Depicts sailing boat flying the Italian flag. Fort Point is at left and the Marin Headlands to the right.
    Oil paintings; Sailboats -- San Francisco Bay (Calif.) -- Pictorial works
  - General John A. Sutter, June 1851; Shaw, Stephen William; BANC PIC 19xx.017--FR; 1 painting on canvas mounted on board: oil; visible image 29 x 23.7 cm. Handwritten title, date, and signature (verso): Gen. John A. Sutter / Painted in June / 1851- / S. W. Shaw / Pinxt.
    Oil paintings; Portraits; Sutter, John Augustus, -- 1803-1880 -- Portraits
  - Mr. Thomas Hardy, 1924; Cartlidge, George; BANC PIC 19xx.030--FR; 1 enameled tile: ceramic; visible image 22.2 x 14.8 cm. Incised title, signature, and date (verso of tile): Mr. Thomas Hardy / O.M., D Litt. (Oxon) / Geo. Cartlidge / sculpt. / 1924; (LR verso): JHB & Cold / S. on. T
    Bust length profile portrait of writer Thomas Hardy (1840-1928).
  - [Asistencia de San Antonio de Pala], [ca. 1910]; Jörgensen, Christian; BANC PIC 19xx.099--FR; 1 painting on canvas mounted on board: oil: visible image 44.5 x 77.5 cm.
    Distant view of mission church buildings with belltower in foreground.
    Oil paintings; Landscapes (Representations) -- California; Spanish mission buildings -- California -- Pictorial works; Asistencia de San Antonio de Pala (Calif.) -- Pictorial works
  - [Mission San Luis Rey de Francia], [ca. 1910]; Jörgensen, Christian; BANC PIC 19xx.100--FR; 1 painting on canvas mounted on board: oil; visible image 46.5 x 71.5 cm. Painted signature (LL): Chris Jörgensen.
    Distant view of southern side of mission church showing western façade in sunlight. Sheep in foreground.
    Oil paintings; Landscapes (Representations) -- California; Spanish mission buildings -- California -- Pictorial works; San Luis Rey Mission (Calif.) -- Pictorial works
  - [The Chagres River, Panama], 1884; Bush, Norton; BANC PIC 19xx.121--FR; 1 painting: oil; visible image 91.5 x 138.5 cm. Painted signature and date (LR): Norton Bush. / 1884.
    Tropical landscape surrounded by vine-laden trees and vegetation. An open hut and small boat on shore with a man, women, children, and a dog. A small boat in the river is visible near a large rock formation in the distance.
    Oil paintings; Landscapes; Rivers -- Montana -- Pictorial works; Landscapes (Representations) -- Panama
  - [Sierra Landscape], 1884; Bush, Norton; BANC PIC 19xx.122--FR; 1 painting: oil; visible image 91 x 128 cm. Painted signature and date (LR, running vertically): Norton Bush. / 1884.
    View overlooking deep valley (ravine) from plateau; trees and bushes in fall color at right. Small trail of smoke in distance.
  - [Cowboy with horse in Arroyo; Indian scouting party approaches]., 1898; Hansen, Herman Wendelborg; BANC PIC 19xx.162--FR; 1 painting on paper: watercolor; visible image 69.3 x 48.7 cm. Painted signature and date (LL): H.W. Hansen / -98.
    Cowboy, with gun at his belt, quiets his horse while watching an Indian scouting party in distance. Jacket, hat, canteen, and knife on ground in foreground.
    Watercolors; West (U.S.) -- Pictorial works; Indians of North America -- West (U.S.) -- Pictorial works; Cowboys -- West (U.S.) -- Pictorial works
  - San Francisco: [Looking up California Street from Montgomery], [1862]; Hildebrandt, Eduard; Wagner, R.; BANC PIC 19xx.172--FR; 1 print: chromolithograph; 27.5 x 37.8 cm. Printed title (LL in image): San Francisco. Printed signature (LR in image): E. Hildebrandt. Handwritten (below print): Looking up California Street from Montgomery.
    Street lined with numerous wooden barrels; two steam trolley cars in center; First Congregational Church, Nob Hill, St. Mary's Cathedral, and the Parrot Building identified. View looking west from Montgomery.
    San Francisco (Calif.) -- Pictorial works; Chromolithographs; Street-railroads -- California -- San Francisco -- Pictorial works; Saint Mary's Cathedral (San Francisco, Calif.) -- Pictorial works; Streets -- California -- San Francisco -- Pictorial works; California Street (San Francisco, Calif.) -- Pictorial works; Nob Hill (San Francisco, Calif.) -- Pictorial works
  - [The Bancroft Company], [ca. 1895]; Dickman, Charles John; BANC PIC 19xx.176--FR; 1 print: lithograph, color; visible image 66.5 x 45 cm. Printed (LC): The Bancroft Company / History building / Market Street / San Francisco; (LL in image): Dickman, del.
    Five story brick building in late Victorian style. The Bancroft Company storefronts selling books and stationary on the left and right of the building entrance. Signs on the building read: The History Company; Publishers; The History building; The Bancroft Company; Booksellers and Stationers. Pedestrians, a small dog, a horsedrawn carriage and wagon bearing a sign from The Bancroft Company stationers are visible in front of building.
    Lithographs -- Color; Bancroft Company -- Pictorial works
  - San Francisco from California Street: drawn from a daguerreotype, the property of Eugene Delessert, Esq.re., c1855; Knoedler, M.; Lemercier; BANC PIC 19xx.245--FR; 1 print: lithograph, b&w; visible image 28.5 x 89 cm. Printed title (LC). Printed (LC) above title: Entered according to Act of Congress in the year 1855, by M. Knoedler...; (LR): Imp. Lemercier, Paris.
    View looking east over city with Yerba Buena Harbor and Island in center, Telegraph Hill and Alcatraz Island at left; various figures in foreground.
    San Francisco (Calif.) -- Pictorial works; Bird's-eye views; Lithographs; California Street (San Francisco, Calif.) -- Pictorial works
  - El Tovar, Grand Canyon, Arizona, on the Santa Fe, 1906; Akin, Louis; BANC PIC 19xx.486--FR; 1 print: lithograph, color; visible image 43 x 90 cm. Printed signature, title, and date (LL): Louis Akin / Grand Canyon / 1906/ Title on plaque (LC on frame).
    View of hotel and adobe pueblo on plateau overlooking canyon. Horse and rider and Indian woman with baby on road.
    Lithographs -- Color; Grand Canyon (Ariz.) -- Pictorial works; Hotel El Tovar -- Pictorial works
  - [Robert Louis Stevenson], 1887; [cast 1895 or later]; Saint-Gaudens, Augustus; BANC PIC 2000.021--FR; 1 bas relief: bronze; diam. 45 cm. In image (UL): To Robert Lewis Stevenson; (UR): Augustus Saint-Gaudens; (ML): MDCCCLXXVII; (LC): Copyright by Augustus Saint-Gaudens. Frame label (verso) from Kennedy & Co. Rare Prints, NY.
    Three-quarter length profile portrait of the author reclining in bed, holding a manuscript.
    Portraits; Stevenson, Robert Louis, -- 1850-1894 -- Portraits
  - [Yosemite Valley], 1879; Herzog, Herman; BANC PIC 2000.072--FR; 1 painting on canvas mounted on board: oil; visible image 55.3 x 73 cm. Painted signature (LR): H. Herzog.; State: Before Treatment (treated 2000).
    Yosemite Valley from Mariposa Trail; El Capitan at left, Bridal Veil Fall and Half Dome at right.
    Oil paintings; Yosemite National Park (Calif.) -- Pictorial works; Yosemite Valley (Calif.) -- Pictorial works
  - Complimentary dinner. G.K. Garrison, Mayor, to the Common Council and Executive Officers of the City of San Francisco, at Robb's, "Court Block," March 11, 1854., Whitton, Towne & Company; ffF869.S3.9.S14498x; 1 item on fabric: ink; 46 x 20.3 cm.
    Dinner menu for Common Council and Executive Officers of the city of San Francisco given at Robb's on March 11, 1854. Includes names of members of council boards. Garrison was mayor of San Francisco from 1853-1854.
    Ephemera; Serigraphy; San Francisco (Calif.) -- History
  - Portland, Oregon: The Metropolis of the Pacific Northwest., c1888; Smith, C. L.; West Shore (Firm: Portland, Or.); BANC PIC 19xx.128--D; 1 print: lithograph, color: sheet 28 x 79 cm. Printed title (LC). Printed signature (LR in image): C.L. Smith. Printed (LL inside of image): Copyrighted 1888. (LL out side of image): 1888 population with suburbs, 60,000; (LR outside of image): Supplement to The West Shore, Portland Oregon.
    Overview of city showing residences, people, and buggies, with Willamette River and Mt. Hood in distance.
    Lithographs -- Color; Bird's-eye views; Portland (Or.) -- Pictorial works
  - Seattle, W.T. [Washington]., 1884; Smith, C. L.; West Shore (Firm: Portland, Or.); Burr, A.; BANC PIC 19xx.125--D; 1 print: lithograph: sheet 30 x 76.5 cm. Printed title (LC). Printed signatures (LR in image): A. Burr, Del; (LL in image): C.L. Smith Lith. Printed (LR): Published by The West Shore, Portland Oregon.
    Overview of city showing residences, business area, docks, Puget Sound, and Mt. Rainier in the distance. Sign on horse drawn wagon in foreground reads: Bell Town.
    Bird's-eye views; Lithographs; Seattle (Wash.) -- Pictorial works
  - The Berkeley Real Estate and Water Works Co: showing the site of the proposed hotel, various water privileges, reservoirs and lands of the company, situated near the State University at Berkeley, Alameda Co. California., 1876; Steinegger, H.; Laver, Augustus; Britton & Rey; BANC PIC 19xx.420--F; 1 print: lithograph, b&w; sheet 71 x 99 cm. Printed title (LC). Printed signature (LR in image): H. Steinegger. Printed (LR out side of image): A. Laver, Archt; (LL): Lith. by Britton, Rey & Co. S.F.; (LC): Entered according to act of Congress in the year one thousand eight hundred and seventy six A.D. by Augustus Laver in the Office of the Librarian in Washington, D.C.; (LC below title): Office: 113 Leidesdorff Street, San Francisco. William Stuart, Secretary. Printed (LR): Officers: H.B. Berryman, President; A.M. Burns; Vice President; William Stuart, Secretary; Augustus Laver, Architect; Thomas Guerin, Hydraulic Engineer; (LL): Trustees: A.P. Bacon, Gen. Agt. Pacific Mail S.S. Co.; A.M. Burns, Prest. Board of Marine Surveyors, H.B. Berryman, of Berryman and Doyle; F. Chappellet, Oakland; P. Ostrander, Engineer San Francisco.
    A birds-eye view of proposed development adjacent to the campus of the University of California, Berkeley.
    Bird's-eye views; Lithographs; Berkeley (Calif.) -- Pictorial works; University of California (1868-1952) -- Pictorial works
  - Bird's-eye-view of the city of Santa Cruz [California]., [ca. 1890?]; Swanton, F.W.; Britton & Rey; BANC PIC 19xx.229--F; 1 print: lithograph, color; sheet 62 x 100 cm Printed title (LC). Printed (LR in image): Photo. lith. by Britton & Rey S.F., copyright F.W. Swanton. Printed explanatory key to locations in image (above title).
    View of city from water showing grounds for Swanton Beach Park, various neighborhoods, Santa Cruz Beach Casino Natatorium Board Walk, and distant hills.
    Lithographs -- Color; Bird's-eye views; Santa Cruz (Calif.) -- Pictorial works
  - Salinas, Cal. [with vignettes of King City and Castroville, California]., 1891; Elliott Pub. Co.; BANC PIC 19xx.191--D; 1 print: lithograph; sheet 54 x 72 cm. Printed title (LC). Printed key to locations in central image (LR and LL). Printed (LC in image): The Elliott Pub. Co. 120 Sutter St. S.F.; (LC below title): Issued by the Salinas Weekly Index, Jan. 1, 1891.